（忆往昔）
我清楚自己想要什么
I know what I want.
但以你的生活方式 我无法如愿
But I can't have it … not how you live.
我正试着淡忘你
I'm trying to get over you.
我们不能打着爱对方的旗号
Just 'cause you love someone.
就肆意妄为地纠缠对方 搅乱对方的生活
Doesn't mean you should stick around and screw up their life.
你很清楚你这是在抛家弃子 是吗
You know you're walking out on your family, right?
对龙你有什么研究嘛
What do you know about dragons?
维斯艾克博士 中古研究系 西蒙菲莎大学
Dr. Visyak. Medieval studies, S.F.U.
鲍比·辛格
Bobby Singer.
下次见他时帮我带句话
Tell him something for me next time you see him.
还是 直接踢他的蛋蛋得了
Actually, just kick him in the jewels.
- 拉斐尔 - 明天你要臣服于我 卡西迪奥
- Raphael… - Tomorrow you kneel, Castiel.
你是想游说我在天堂发起内战么
Are you proposing that I start a civil war in heaven?
答对了哟
Ding! Ding! Ding!
- 巴尔萨泽 - 我当然乐意帮你
- Balthazar. - Of course I want to help you.
发动战争所需的能量
I mean, the amount of power that it would take.
非常强大
To mount a war …
但如果我说我知道如何拥有最强的能量呢
But what if I said I knew how to go nuclear?
炼狱
Purgatory.
你勾结了克劳力试图找到炼狱
You and crowley have been going after purgatory together?
- 杀了温家兄弟 - 不行
- Just kill the winchesters. - No.
那我就只好亲自出马了
Then I'll do it myself.
如果你胆敢碰他们一根毫毛
If you touch a hair on their heads,
我就毁掉我们的协议
I will tear it all down … our arrangement.
晚上好 迪恩
Hello, Dean.
你就如同我另一个弟弟一般
You are like a brother to me.
所以 如果我阻止你做什么的时候
So, if I'm asking you not to do something,
你得相信我 兄弟
You got to trust me, man.
否则呢
Or what?
否则我就将不昔一切地阻止你
Or I'll have to do what I have to do to stop you.
对不起了 迪恩
I'm sorry, Dean.
（如今）
（1937年3月15日）
（普维敦斯 罗得岛）
（完）
谁
Hello?
是谁
求求你
Please…
我们不知道
We didn't know.
对不起
I'm sorry!
（猎黑行者 作者 H·P·洛夫克拉夫特 1937年3月15日）
[邪恶力量 第6季第21集]
行了 至少你尽力了 不是吗
Well, you know what? At least you tried.
确实 一点用都没有
Yeah, a fat lot of good it did.
但他为什么还要出现呢
Why did he even come, right?
萨穆埃尔的日记屁用没有
Well, Samuel's journals are pointless.
原谅我的无礼 但
I mean, I'm sorry, but, uh,
杰毕戴·坎贝尔可没提
Jebediah Campbell has squat to tell me.
怎么阻止小卡打开炼狱
about how to stop Cass from cracking purgatory.
事实上 并不是我们手上这些资料没用
Well, actually, it's not about the journals we have.
而是因为我们没有找对正主
It's about the one we don't.
什么意思
Meaning what?
是个坏消息
Well, that's the bad news.
我们的搭档小卡那天晚上可不是来认错的
Our pal Cass didn't stop in last night just to mend fences.
他干了什么
What did he do?
- 偷走了些东西 - 啥东西
- Stole something. - What?
摩西·坎贝尔的一本日记
The journal of one Moishe Campbell.
摩西
"Moishe"?
纽约州的坎贝尔家族
Of the New York Campbells.
那我们得把它找回来 对吗
Uh, so we got to get it back, right?
或是直接看我之前弄的复印本
Or just read the copy I had already made.
两位好 我是偏执狂鲍比·辛格
Hi. Glad to meet you. Bobby singer, paranoid bastard.
我好像找到条线索
I think I zeroed in on something.
有啥发现
What do you got?
去跟霍华德·飞利浦聊了聊三月十日的事
"Went to talk to Howard Phillips about the events of March 10th."
是1937年3月10日
That's March 10, 1937.
了解 不过这菲利普斯是谁来着
All right, so, who's this Phillips guy?
菲利普斯可不是他的姓 他是洛夫克萊夫特
Phillips ain't his last name. It's Lovecraft.
等下 H·P·洛夫克萊夫特吗
Wait … H.P. Lovecraft?
给我瞧瞧
Let me see that.
他很有名还是怎么着
Am I supposed to know who that is?
恐怖小说作家
Horror writer?
《疯狂山脉》
"At the mountains of madness, "
《克苏鲁的呼唤》
"The call of cthulhu."
知道了
Yeah.
我之前光忙着和女人翻云覆雨了
No, I'm … I was too busy having sex with women.
总而言之 在他的小说里
Well, anyhow, there's one notion that comes up.
一次次地提到同一件事
over and over again in his stories …
就是打开别个空间之门 让可怕的东西穿行
Namely, opening doors to other dimensions and letting scary crap through.
是嘛
You don't say.
所以你觉得洛夫克萊夫特对炼狱有所了解
Wait, so you're saying you think Lovecraft knew something about purgatory?
我能肯定的就是 摩西去拜访过他
All I know is, Moishe paid him a visit.
噢 不
Oh! No!
放 放了她
Just … just let her go.
好吗 放
Okay, just …
不
No!
本
Ben?
- 有人闯进家里 - 什么
- There's men in the house. - What?
他们杀了马特 抓了妈妈
They killed Matt. They got Mom.
他们来了 我能听到
They're coming. I hear them.
- 他们是什么 - 我不知道
- What are they? - I-I don't know.
- 你看到他们的眼睛了吗 - 没有
- Did you see their eyes? - No.
- 牙齿呢 - 没有
- Teeth? - No.
- 这很重要 本 我必须知道 - 迪恩 我不知道
- This is important, Ben. I need to know. - Dean, I don't know.
- 本 你现在在哪儿 - 在我房间里
- Ben, where are you now? - In my room.
能接近你妈的衣柜吗
Can you get to your mom's closet?
那里有我留下的散弹枪
I left a shotgun in there.
不行 迪恩 我怎么办
No! Dean, what do I do?
本 听我的
Okay, Ben, listen to me.
去窗边 然后跳下去
Go to your window… and jump.
- 什么 - 断几根骨头
- What?! - Any bones you break.
比起他们要对你做的事可好多了
won't compare to what they're gonna do to you, Ben.
- 你必须跳出去 - 好吧 我这就跳
- You've got to jump. - Okay, I'm going.
我马上来
I'm coming right now.
我会救出你们母子俩的 我保证
I'm gonna get you and your mom, I promise.
还在吗 本
You with me, Ben?
本
Ben?
Ben!
你好啊 迪恩
Hello, Dean.
想聊聊吗
Fancy a chat?
天啊
God.
多久了 迪恩
How long is being, Dean.
从我上次假死算起
Since my so-called demise, yes?
克劳力 放他们走
Crowley, let them go now.
否则我发誓
Or I swear …
对对
Right, right.
你会在我身上开各种洞
You'll rip me a cornucopia of orifices.
我先跟你说说现在的情况吧
Let's get to the bit where I tell you how this goes.
你在我的菜盘子里搅和太久了
Your chocolate's been in my peanut butter for far too long.
我要杀了你
I'm going to kill you.
迪恩 总这么风趣
Oh, Dean. Ever the wit.
我手上有你的 什么来的
I've got your … what are they? …
前女性朋友和一个小大人
Ex-ladyfriend and not-kid,
除非你别再管我的闲事儿
and I'm keeping them until I'm satisfied.
否则我就不放人
that you've backed the hell off.
我告诉你 再不放人就别怪我不客气
I'm telling you … last chance to let 'em go easy.
你威胁人的时候真可爱
You're adorable when you get all threatening.
别担心 我不会伤害他们
Don't worry … I won't hurt them,
前提是你和绿巨人让开道
Provided you and Jolly green stand down.
明白了么 很好
Got it? Splendid.
么么
Kisses.
怎么回事
What's the story?
他说只要我们老实呆着
He said Lisa and Ben keep breathing…
莉莎和本就能活命
As long as we sit on our thumbs.
你觉得小卡知道这事吗
You think Cass knows about this?
得假设他知道
We got to assume he does.
那我们要怎么办
So what are we gonna do?
我可以告诉你我们不要做的事
I'll tell you what we're not gonna do …
干坐着
Sit here.
- 我去找他们 - 我跟你去
- I'm going after 'em. - I'm coming with.
不 萨姆
No, Sam.
你和鲍比继续查洛夫克萊夫特这事
You and Bobby stay on the Lovecraft thing, okay?
小卡已经先我们好几步了
Cass is already way ahead of us.
你傻了 我不可能让你一人去的
You got to be nuts if you think I'm gonna let you do this alone.
鲍比可以自己查
Bobby can take care of the case.
- 不行 兄弟们 - 鲍比
- No, guys. - Bobby…
这事非同小可 我们不能现在放弃
This is a big ball. Okay? We can't drop it now.
好吧
Fine.
那你俩要怎么找到莉莎和本
Then how are you two gonna find Lisa and Ben?
不好意思 孩子们
I'm sorry, boys.
你们看我像男仆吗
Do I look like a manservant to you?
不像吗 那就别召唤我了 谢谢
No? No? Then quit ringing for me. Please.
这事很重要 巴尔萨泽
This is important, Balthazar.
我刚刚正在
I was drinking a '75 dom.
一个女歌手的肚脐上吸75年的廊酒呢
Out of a soprano's navel when you called.
那才是要事
That was important.
克劳力还活着
Crowley's alive.
小爷我早知道了
Well, you've been scooped.
小卡告诉我了
Cass already told me.
那小卡有没有告诉你
Well, did Cass tell you.
他和克劳力变成好基友了
that he is Crowley's butt buddy,
你个臭屁的混蛋
you smug little dick?
- 什么 - 君子交易
- Excuse me? - Handshake deal.
平分炼狱中的所有灵魂
Go halfsies on all the souls of purgatory …
他告诉你这个了吗
He fill you in on that?
是的 是的 当然说了
Well, yes, yes. Yes, of course he did. Yes.
当然了
Oh, yes, of course. I … I …
你就别装了
We can read it all over your face.
克劳力和小卡抓走了两个
Crowley and Cass took two people.
对我来说很重要的人
who are very important to me.
为什么我要关心这些
And I care about this because…
因为没准有那么一丝的正义感
Because maybe there is a shred of decency.
隐藏在你这臭皮囊下
Underneath this … this snarky crap.
他们是无辜的
They're innocent people,
我求你了 帮帮我
And I'm asking for your help.
知道了
I see.
很好
Fair enough.
操你妈
Son of a bitch!
迪恩 还是找小卡吧
Look, Dean, let's just call Cass.
- 也许他并不知道 - 我们不能叫小卡
- Maybe he doesn't know anything about… - We are not calling Cass.
- 可是 迪恩 - 我们不找小卡
- Yeah, but, Dean… - we're not calling cass!
那怎么办
So what, then?
你知道 恐怖小说 挺三俗
You know, uh, horror … lowbrow.
说没什么内含 没问题
Put us in the ghetto, fine.
但是洛夫克拉夫特这人很有文采
But H.P. Lovecraft … this guy is literature.
他应该被编入教科书
I mean, he … he should be taught in schools.
他应该和狄更斯与丁·雷·昆士齐名
He's up there with Dickens and…Dean R. Koontz.
真的
Seriously.
这和我作品中呈现出的观点
Well, that's … that's definitely.
简直如出一辙
The angle I'm taking with my piece.
好吧
Oh, okay. Okay.
不好意思 你可以 请
Sorry. You can … please, please.
我听说你收集了大量的
So, I hear you have a large collection.
洛夫克拉夫特私人信件
of Lovecraft's private letters.
是的
Yeah.
世上最多
World's largest.
肯定很受妹子青睐吧
You must be catnip to the ladies.
我正在进行一段长期的网恋
I'm in a long-term online relationship, so…
我想问一下关于洛夫克萊夫特
Well, I'd like to ask you about.
生前最后几年的事情
Lovecraft's last years …
尤其是
specifically.
在1937年3月10日左右
anything that might have gone down.
发生过什么吗
around March 10, 1937.
那个…
Okay.
你在与另一个人合作调查此事吗
A-are you working on this with the other guy?
另一个人
Other guy?
对 那人穿着风衣 表情超呆
Yeah, uh, you know, trenchcoat, looks like Columbo,
说话像雨人
talks like rain man?
这样啊
Right.
我们是…竞争关系
W-we're…competitors.
两家敌对的杂志社
Rival magazines.
好吧
Okay.
好吧 我当时是这么告诉他的
Okay, well, um, I'll tell you what I told him.
3月10日 霍华德举办了一场晚宴
Howard had a dinner party on March 10th.
晚宴
Party?
宴会上请到了多少朋友
How many friends at this party?
六个
Well, six …
这里所谓的朋友
If by "friends" you mean.
指的是黑魔法邪教的信徒们
co-worshippers in a black-magic cult.
他们当晚齐聚一堂 准备举行一场仪式
They were getting together that night to perform a ritual.
非同小可
Something big.
有多严重
Define "big."
不算什么 不过是开启通往
Not much. Just open a door.
另一维度的大门而已
into another dimension.
他们为什么要那么做
Why would they do that?!
想见识一下那边的世界 说不定很祥和
To see what's out there … you know, maybe it's friendly.
怎么可能
It's never friendly!
其实我也是猜的
I mean…I imagine.
那么 咒语起效了吗
So, did it work … the spell?
第二天的早报并没有提到
Well, uh, there was no mention of cthulhu.
什么灵异事件
in the morning papers, so…
事实上 我手上刚好
Actually, I do happen to have.
有几封信提到了那场晚宴
several letters detailing the dinner.
但最糟糕的情况也不过是宿醉而已
Worst thing that was reported was a hangover,
所以说…
So it's, uh…
我把它们放在这里了
Got it … I've got them right here.
有些细节 其实很有意思
Some … it's actually pretty interesting.
呃…我就放在…
Um, and … and they were…
我明明就放在…
They were … they were right th…
我明明放在这里面了
They were right here.
又不可能有隐形人突然现身
Well, it's not like an invisible guy.
把它们偷走了 对吧
could just pop in and steal 'em, right?
没错 没错
Right. Right.
你再仔细想想
Oh, uh, I'll leave you to it,
找到以后打电话通知我 好吗
And, uh, you call me if you find 'em, huh?
好的
Okay, hey…
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢你能抽时间过来
Thanks again for dropping by, huh?
洛夫克萊夫特曾试图撬开该死的维度之门
Lovecraft tried to jimmy a damn dimensional door.
傻帽
Idjit.
那结果如何呢
So, what happened?
什么也没发生…
Oh, nothing much…
但经过我的调查
Except I dug.
发现晚宴上到场的所有来宾
And every guest invited to the hoedown …
在一年之内全部死亡或失踪了
dead or disappeared inside a year.
那你现在准备去哪里
Wow. Um, so, where are you off to now?
去和其中一位来宾聊聊
Have a chat with one of the guests.
等等 你刚不是说到场的都死了吗
Wait, didn't you just say that everyone there died?
洛夫克萊夫特邀请的人都死了
Yeah, everybody Lovecraft invited died.
但他的女仆有个九岁的儿子
Seems the maid had a 9-year-old boy.
当时也在现场
He was there.
那他现在差不多有83岁了吧 他在哪里
So he'd be, what, 83 years old now? Where is he?
自从那晚之后 他就没去过别的地方
Same place he's been ever since the big night …
一直被关在精神病院里
locked in a mental ward.
懂了
I see.
有情况随时通知我 好吗
Well, keep me posted, huh?
好的 保持联络
Okay. Stay in touch.
你那边情况如何
How's things going there?
有莉莎和本的线索吗
You got a lead on Lisa and Ben?
我们正在进行审问
Well, we're making a few inquiries.
进展很慢
Slow going.
迪恩的情况怎样
How's Dean?
你应该能想象得到
About how you'd expect.
下一位顾客
Next customer.
听着 我什么都不知道
Look, I don't know anything.
好吧 那就走着瞧
Yeah, we'll see.
迪恩
Dean?
怎么了
Yeah?
哥们 酒和咖啡什么的
Look, man, y-you're running on, what, uh,
你从刚才就一直喝
whiskey and coffee and whatever else you're taking.
那又怎样
Yeah, and?
我们这么做不过是绝望之举
And we're grasping at straws here, man.
只要我杀恶魔杀够数
Look, I kill enough of these demons,
最终会有人告诉我克劳力的下落
Eventually one of them's gonna tell me where Crowley is.
没问题了吧
So, we good?
你审问他们很久了
Well, look, you've been at it for a while.
起码让我替你一会吧
Why don't you at least let me take over?
- 你该歇歇了 - 不用了 谢谢
- You deserve a break. - No, thanks.
- 迪恩 - 萨姆 别管闲事
- Dean … - Sam, back off.
莉莎和本
Lisa and Ben …
不管他们在哪里 都是我害的
Wherever they are, that is 100% on me.
如果他们出什么事…
And if they are hurt…
需要的时候我会喊你
I'll yell if I need you.
卡西迪奥 是萨姆
Castiel, it's Sam.
我不知道本和莉莎的事是不是你干的
So, look, I don't know if you're in on this whole Ben/Lisa thing,
但是你哪怕还有一点良知
But if you have any heart whatsoever,
那就把他们放回来
bring them back to us, man.
行行好
Come on.
拜托了
Please.
求你了
I'm begging you.
我求求你了 你懂不懂啊
I am begging you. Do you understand?
宝贝儿
Sweetie…
你看起来好紧张
you look tense.
你抓走了本和莉莎
You took Ben and Lisa.
那个呀
Oh. That.
我跟你说过了
I told you…
不要动萨姆和迪恩
Not to touch Sam and Dean.
我尊重你的意愿了
I've respected that.
我只是钻了个明显的空子
I'm merely exploiting the obvious loophole.
只要那女人和那孩子在我手里
As long as I have the woman and the boy,
你那两个花里胡哨的小英雄
your fop-coiffed little heroes.
就会掘地三尺地找他们
will be scouring the earth for them.
而不会来找我们的麻烦了
Therefore, not you and not me.
一举多得
Everybody wins.
你该先跟我商量的
You should have talked to me first.
我宁可先斩后奏
I'd rather ask forgiveness than permission.
他们在哪 克劳力
Where are they, Crowley?
你不许伤害他们
You are not to harm them.
听清了吗
Do you understand me?
你猜咋的
You know what?
你已经为那些人类操心得够多的了
You're maxed out on putting humans out of bounds.
哥爱干啥干啥
I'll do with them as I please.
你想阻止哥
You want to stop me?
就去把炼狱给我找到
Go find friggin' purgatory!
超声波电话响了啊
Call on the bat phone?
总挑你休息时间找你 是吧
Never call during business hours, do they?
我会回来的
I'll be back.
小卡 小卡 小卡 你能来真好
Cass, Cass, Cass. So good of you to come.
巴尔萨泽 你召唤我做什么
Balthazar, why'd you summon me here?
我就有话直说了行么
Can I ask you a direct question?
当然了
Of course.
你跟地狱之王在狼狈为奸吗
Are you in flagrante with the king of hades?
当然没有
Of course not.
你一直不会撒谎
Always were such a terrible liar.
这么说是真的了
So it's true.
好吧
All right, then.
为什么
Why?
是结束这一切的方法
It's a means to an end.
巴尔萨泽 你懂的
Balthazar, you understand that.
那是当然了
Oh, absolutely.
但你说的结束到底指的什么
What's the end here, exactly?
是洗劫炼狱
You know, raid purgatory,
- 把灵魂都抓走吗 - 是赢得战争
- snatch up all the souls? - Win the war.
那我只能认为你就是那个皮囊 是吗
And I can only assume that you'd be the vessel, correct?
把那些灵魂都吸入你体内 所有的能量
Suck up all those souls into yourself, all that power.
这是唯一的办法
It's the only way.
你消化不了那么多能量 你会爆炸
Or too much juice for you, in which case you explode,
地球也会跟着遭殃
taking a substantial chunk of the planet along with you.
- 不会那样的 - 是啊 是啊
- That won't happen. - Sure, sure.
当然了
Of course.
不过
Just…
你能说这是完全没风险的吗
just tell me that it's entirely risk-free.
对不起我之前没告诉你 不过我要知道
I'm sorry that I didn't tell you, but I need to know.
你是不是站在我这边
Are you with me or not?
要知道 你可能挺靠谱 不过
You know, you may be certifiable, but…
好吧
Fine.
一不做
In for a penny…
二不休
in for a pound.
你到底怎么知道的
How'd you hear about this, anyway?
你的小吼猴们说的
Oh, your howler monkeys, of course.
他们对绑架的事
See, they're just a touch worked up.
都挺火大的呢
about that kidnapping business, you know.
你真不是跟那个记者一伙的吗
You're sure you're not with that other reporter?
那个穿风衣的
In the coat?
那个人是骗子 是个冒牌货
Liar, that one, not who he says.
不 先生
No, sir.
我跟他
Uh, I'm not…
不是一个报社的
affiliated with his paper.
我就想问你几个问题
I just have a couple of questions.
关于1937年你参加的那个晚宴聚会
about a dinner party you were at in 1937.
大家都那么着迷
Everyone's so fascinated.
都想知道我在伟大的
Want to know about my night.
洛夫克萊夫特家渡过的那晚到底如何
at the home of the great H.P. Lovecraft?
要是您愿意说
If you don't mind.
你都听过那个故事了
Well, you know the story.
他们念了咒语 他们都说是失败了
They did their spell, and they all said it failed.
你相信有怪物吗
Do you believe in monsters?
信
Yup.
你知道 你说这种话
You know, you go saying that,
他们会把你终生关在这儿
they'll lock you in here rest of your life.
不管你看到了什么
Whatever you saw…
你告诉我 我都信
you tell me, and I'll buy it straight.
那咒语成功了
The spell worked.
打开了一扇门 有东西进来了
A door opened, and something came through.
但那东西是隐形的 所以大家都不知道
B-but it was invisible, so no one knew.
除了我
Except me.
那你是怎么知道的
How did you know, then?
因为它带走了我妈妈
Because it took my mother!
占据了她的身体
It went into her.
她就变了 甚至闻起来都不同了
She wasn't the same. She even smelled different.
后来她就消失了
And then she disappeared.
然后 奇怪的是
And, surprise, surprise…
一个接着一个 他们都死掉了
one by one, they all start dying.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry…
你妈妈的事
about your mom.
你是第一个说这话的人
You're the first person ever said that.
嘿 想看张照片吗
Hey. You want to see a picture?
我勒个去
I'll be damned.
我保证 伙计
I promise you, pal…
快招了吧
You start talking…
不然我发誓
…Or I swear.
我会把你活剥了
I will rip your skin off,
一刀一刀地割
strip by strip.
然后我再杀了你
And then I'm gonna kill you.
我会用同样的方式对待下一个恶魔
And then I'm gonna do it to the next demon.
你听清楚了吗
You hear me?
清楚了
Yeah.
一清二楚
I hear you.
那你可以闭嘴了 卑鄙的混蛋
So you can stop talking, you miserable sack.
我没要你帮我
I didn't ask for your help.
不管怎样 不用谢
Well, regardless, you're welcome.
你怎么来了
Why are you here?
我没想到克劳力会带走莉莎和本
I had no idea Crowley would take Lisa and Ben.
对 没错
Yeah, right.
你不相信我
You don't believe me.
我不相信你嘴里蹦出的任何话
I don't believe a word that's coming out of your mouth.
你说过 我们像一家人一样
I thought you said that we were like family.
我也这么觉得 信任不该是双向的吗
Well, I think that, too. Shouldn't trust run both ways?
小卡 我做不到
Cass, I just can't.
迪恩 你有求我必应
Dean, I do everything that you ask.
你一召唤 我马上出现
I always come when you call.
我是你的朋友
And I am your friend.
虽然你还是不相信我
Still, despite your lack of faith in me.
加上你还在威胁我
and now your threats…
我还是 又救了你一命
…I just saved you, yet again.
除了你的家人 谁会为你付出这么多
Is anyone but your closest kin has ever done more for you?
我只求一件事
All I ask is this one thing.
相信你的炼狱计划吗
Trust your plan to pop purgatory?
迪恩 那是我应得的
I've earned that, Dean.
我是来告诉你 我会去找莉莎和本
I came to tell you that I will find Lisa and Ben.
我会带他们回来
And I will bring them back.
做我的后援 先别插手
Stand behind me…
这是我唯一一次求你
The one time I ask.
你是让我坐视不理吗
You're asking me to stand down?
迪恩
Dean …
你的要求和克劳力的要求是一样的
That's the same damn ransom note that Crowley handed me.
你知道 对吧
You know that, right?
不用了 谢谢
Well, no, thanks.
我自己去找他们
I'll find them myself.
你还是回到克劳力的身边
In fact, why don't you go back to Crowley.
然后告诉他 你俩都去死吧
and tell him that I said you can both kiss my ass?
鲍比
Bobby?
埃莉
Ellie.
好久不见
It's been a while.
请进
Come in.
你怎么找到我的
So, how did you find me?
埃莉 虽然我们相处的时间不长
Well, we weren't together long, Ellie, but, uh,
但是我知道一点你的事情
I know a thing or two about you.
我知道你的安全屋
I know your safehouses.
我告诉你 这里也不是绝对安全
And let me tell you … this one ain't all that safe.
你就是来聊天的吗
So, did you come here just to, um, chat?
埃莉 我知道你是什么
I know what you are, Ellie.
你不是从密尔沃基来的 对吧
You're not exactly from Milwaukee, are you?
对
Not exactly.
这点我不介意
And … not that I'd have minded,
但是你也谎报了年龄
but you kind of fibbed about your age, too.
就谎报了一点
Just slightly.
九百年
900 years.
好吧 你到底搞什么把戏
Okay, so, what's your game, then?
把戏
Game?
你为什么来这里
Yeah. Why are you here?
夏娃一出现 立马弄得满城风雨
Eve came through and raised all kinds of hell quickly.
你在这里这么久了
You been here how long?
一直没举动是怎么回事
What's with the slow burn?
- 我们不一样啊 - 怪物吗
- Well, you know, we're not all alike. - Monsters?
如果叫我怪物可以让你开心点 可以
Okay, if it makes you feel better to call me that, fine.
你从炼狱来的
You're from freakin' purgatory.
你和我上床的时候
You never thought to mention that.
都没想过要告诉我吗
the whole time you slept with me?
鲍比 我就是我
I am what I am, Bobby.
我还是你的朋友哦
And I happen to be a friend.
你想要给我个解释吗
You want to explain that to me?
我可没让那些白痴打开炼狱之门
I didn't ask those idiots to crack the door.
我就碰巧钻了出来
I just happened to be the thing that fell through.
我告诉你 出来的是我 算你走运
And let me tell you something … you are lucky it was me.
你说你和我们是同一阵营的
You're saying you're on our side?
我独自为营 我只是喜欢这个地方
I'm on my side. I happen to like it here.
我不想看到这个地方
I don't want to see this place.
变得横尸遍野
turned into some bloody wasteland.
所以你杀了洛夫克萊夫特
So you killed H.P. Lovecraft.
拜托 他连「你好」都不会写
Please. That guy couldn't even write "hello."
我花了七十五年的时间 紧闭炼狱之门
I have spent 75 years trying to keep purgatory closed.
你觉得我为什么要给迪恩那把剑
Why do you think I gave Dean the sword?
是为了阻止夏娃
To stop Eve.
你们应该杀了那些该死的龙
Hell, you guys were supposed to kill the damn dragons!
听着
Look.
这些都可以归咎到一个天使身上
This all comes down to one angel.
他想要炼狱 他也在找你
He wants purgatory, and he's looking for you.
谢谢提醒
Well, thanks for the heads up.
我了解他 小埃
I know him, El.
他会想尽办法达成目的
He's gonna figure it out one way or another.
阻止他的唯一方法就是 先他一步
Now, the only way I can stop him is to get ahead of him.
所以我要知道怎么打开炼狱之门
So I need to know how you open the door.
不行
No.
不行鲍比 不能告诉任何人 太危险了
No, Bobby. It's too dangerous for anyone to know.
如果我能找到你
If I found you…
他也不远了
he ain't far behind.
至少让我带你走
At least let me take you somewhere,
让我保护你
protect you.
不用了
No.
谢谢
Thanks.
我还有其他的藏身之处 别担心
I have a couple other places lined up. Don't worry.
鲍比
Bobby.
你只是个人类
You're just a man.
我自己可以保护好我自己
I'm better off protecting myself.
萨姆 喝酒解愁呢
Drinking your feelings, sam?
我还以为那是你哥哥的风格
I thought that was your brother's bag.
最近压力大
Stressful times.
那好 我们得谈谈
Well, we need to talk.
为啥
Why?
因为
Because …
我知道以后我肯定要后悔 但是
I know I'm gonna live to regret this, but…
我现在正式加入你们
I'm officially on your team.
你们几个混蛋
You bastards.
我们凭什么相信你
And we should believe you why?
难道你不相信我还是有那么点正义感吗
Would you believe I had a shred of decency?
不相信
No.
这么直接 太伤人了
Oh, that hurts.
好吧 你说的对 我也是为了生存
Okay, you're right. It's survival.
我问过小卡几个问题
You see, I asked Cass some questions,
我对他的回答很不满意
And I disliked his answers.
他好像疯了一样的相信自己
He seems awfully sure of himself.
能够吸收那么巨大的能量
for a man who wants to swallow a million nuclear reactors.
他这么做
I mean, these things.
不会有什么好下场的
can get a bit Chernobyl, you know.
所以就是这样
So, voila.
就当我是双重间谍
Consider me your double agent.
另外我擅自去找过你们的朋友
Oh, and I took the liberty of searching for your friends.
花了点时间 克劳力很狡猾
Took a while … crowley's a clever one.
你找到他们了吗
You found them?
好消息是找到了
The upside is yes.
但坏消息是也没有
The downside is, no,
我没法把他们带出来
I can't get them for you.
为什么呢 … 因为克劳力满栋楼都画着
Why not? … Because Crowley's angel-proofed.
天使防护阵
the whole bloody building.
我觉得他不信任小卡
I guess he doesn't trust Cass.
似乎他俩的婚后生活挺顺利啊
Seems that marriage is going swimmingly.
那好 你带我们过去 越近越好
Okay, well, get us as close as you can.
行
Sure.
但之后就靠你们自己了
But then you're on your own.
好了 只能送到这儿了
All right, boys, this is where I get off.
上帝保佑…
God be with you…
神马的
Or what have you.
小心点
All right, be careful.
迪恩 太好了
Oh, dean. Thank god.
我带你们出去
Still got to get you out of here.
没事的
okay.
走
Let's go.
想把小崽子带走 门儿都没有
The brat's not going anywhere.
我也别想带走
And neither am I.
克劳力就知道你可能会来
Crowley thought you might come.
保险起见 他让我附到
So he had me jump this hot little piece of ass.
这辣妹身上
For insurance.
可不能没了筹码啊 对吧
Can't go losing our leverage, now, can we?
你再靠近一步
Ah! Another step…
免费的阑尾切除手术
…Free appendectomy.
你妈妈现在意识很清醒
You know, she's awake in here … your mom.
我能听到她的想法
I can hear her thinking.
- 本 别听她的 - 什么
- Don't listen to her, ben. - What?
我不过是想告诉他 你是他真正的父亲
I was just gonna tell him that you're his real daddy.
开个玩笑
Just kidding.
没人知道你父亲是谁 小屁孩
Who knows who your real dad is, kid?
你妈是个婊子
Your mom's a slut.
你丫的给我闭嘴
You shut your mouth!
干嘛 现在想英雄救美了
Oh, what? You're her white knight now?
她后悔认识了你 迪恩
She wishes she never met you, dean.
认识你是她这辈子最大的错误
You're the worst mistake she ever made!
算第二吧
Well, second worst…
自从有了你之后
After keeping you.
本 那不是你妈 她在说谎
That's not your mom, ben. She's lying.
你个从小缺乏父爱的有什么资格说话
Says the c-minus lay with 10 miles of daddy issues.
你每天晚上都是怎么过的啊
Whatever gets you through the night, tiny tim.
别过来 小子
Ah-ah-ah. Back off, cowboy.
知道吗 她在求我杀了你
You know, she's begging me to kill you.
你妈说是你拖她后腿
She says you hold her back.
自从你生下来之后 她从来没快活过
Never had a lick of fun since you were born.
本 看着我 看我这
Ben, look at me. Look at me.
你一定会没事的
You're gonna be just fine.
本 刀子
Ben, knife!
怎么了迪恩 打我啊
What's the matter, dean? Hit me.
你是不想伤害到莉莎啊
Oh, you don't want to hurt poor Lisa?
[咒语]
给我闭嘴
Shut your mouth!
[咒语]
停下来
Stop it.
我警告你 … 滚回地狱去 你这个黑眼婊子
I'm warning you. … You can go to hell, you black-eyed bitch.
你确定嘛
You sure about that?
妈妈
Mom!
继续驱逐我啊
Exorcise me now…
她现在不过是具行尸走肉
She's just a dead meatsuit.
你想说什么来着
Now, what was it you wanted to say?
[咒语]
- 妈妈 - 莉莎
- Mom! - Lisa!
莉莎 看着我
Lisa. Look at me.
用力摁住 好吗
Here, put pressure on that, okay?
我知道很疼 宝贝 我知道
I know, honey. I know.
没事的没事的
It's all right, it's all right, it's ok.
我是萨姆 有事请留言
It's Sam. Leave me a message.
萨姆 你死哪里去了
Sam, where are you, damn it?!
本 我们得把她弄出去
All right, Ben. We got to get her out of here, okay?
本
Ben.
Ben?
本
Ben.
听着 小伙子 你得振作起来
Listen, man, I need you to pull it together, okay?
坚强些 你母亲现在正需要你
You got to be strong. Your mom needs you right now.
到行李袋里拿上盐弹枪
Go over in that duffel bag. Grab the salt gun.
我得抱你妈妈出去
I got to carry your mom out,
要是有东西要袭击我们 你就开枪
so if anything comes at us, you shoot it.
- 可是 - 现在就去
- But … - Go. Now.
好的 刀 带上刀
Okay. Get the knife. Get the knife.
好了 本 手肘夹紧
All right, Ben. Keep your elbow in,
枪抵肩膀 听我指示
gun tight to your shoulder, and watch for the kick.
本
Ben!
Ben.
- 本 - 迪恩
- Ben! - Dean.
快 振作点儿
Come on! Pull it together!
你不想救你妈妈了吗 快走
You want your mom to die?! Let's go.
跟上
Come on.
- 迪恩 - 萨姆
- Dean! - Sam?
我在这里
I'm in here!
快走 我们得去医院
Come on. We got to get to a hospital.
本 把枪给他
Ben. Give the gun to him.
萨姆 开辆车来
Sam, we need a ride.
走 快走
Go, go, go, go.
她没事 本 她没事的
She's fine, Ben. She's fine.
她会没事的 马上就到医院了
She's gonna be just fine. We're almost there.
别睡 坚持住
Hey. Hey. Hey. Stay with me.
萨姆 再开快点
Sam, you got to go faster, man.
你会没事的 你会好好的
You're gonna be fine. You're gonna be just fine.
本 对不起
Ben, I'm sorry.
本
Ben.
你来干嘛
What do you want?
迪恩 听我说
Dean, listen.
你想听我说什么
What do you want me to say?
她根本撑不过今晚
She'll be dead by midnight.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不在乎
I don't care.
说什么都没用了
It's too little, too late.
好吧
Okay.
反正我也不是为你而来
Well, regardless, I didn't come for you.
什么意思
Meaning?
她现在没事了
She's fine now.
很快就会醒了
She'll wake soon.
迪恩 我是真心诚意的向你道歉
Dean, I said I'm sorry, and I meant it.
谢了
Thank you.
我也希望覆水能收
I wish this changed anything.
我懂
I know.
我也是
So do I.
不管怎样 我只想尽力弥补
All else aside, I just wanted to fix what I could.
还有件事你能帮我
There's one more thing you could do for me.
妈妈
Hey, mom.
怎么
What …
你在医院
You're in the hospital.
- 怎么了 - 我们出车祸了
- What happened? - We were in a car crash.
- 你没事吧 - 是的是的 我很好
- Are you okay? - Yeah, yeah. I'm … I'm fine.
你头部撞得挺重
You hit your head pretty bad,
但你现在没事啦
but you're okay now.
你是谁
Who are you?
我 叫迪恩
I-I'm Dean.
是我撞了你们
Um… I'm the guy who hit you.
我就是
I just, uh…
我当时有点失控
I lost control for a minute.
就是想来说声抱歉
And I just wanted to say that I'm sorry.
很高兴你们两位都没事
But I'm real happy you two are both okay.
还有
And, uh…
我也 很高兴你们的生活又能恢复从前了
…I'm just … I'm glad your life can get back to normal now.
我们都很好
We're okay, so…
这才重要 不是吗
so that's what's important, right?
没错
Yeah.
那么
Anyway, uh…
我就先走了
I'll leave you two alone.
好好照顾你妈妈
You take care of your mom.
怎么样
Well?
没怎么样
Well, nothing.
迪恩 你以前是干过不少蠢事
Dean, you know, you have pulled some shady crap before,
但这绝对是最烂的一遭
but this has got to be the worst.
掩盖他们的记忆
Whitewashing their memories?
作为一个过来人 我劝你一句
Take it from somebody who knows …
要是你再跟我提莉莎和本
If you ever mention Lisa or Ben to me again,
我就打断你的鼻子
I will break your nose.
迪恩 … 我没在开玩笑
Dean … i'm not kidding.